unb.ca 2012-05-23

# UNB | Privacy

The University of New Brunswick is committed to protecting your personal information.

## Personal information is not collected automatically

Personal information is not automatically collected from you when you visit UNB’s website.  You may choose to provide personal information via web form or email when applying for a university service or when using our web feedback form.  Any personal information that you provide will be protected in accordance with applicable privacy laws and UNB policy.

Additionally, members of the UNB community may log in to secure pages, using their unique UNB login ID.  The UNB login ID may be stored in a log along with the uniform resource locator of the secure page(s) that were visited. However, the content displayed on those pages is not stored.

## Information gathered automatically

UNB's web server logs some information about Internet traffic on its pages. These logs capture aggregate, generic, non-personal identifying information about visitors such as the type of browser used, pages visited and duration of stay. This information is used to help us understand our Internet traffic and improve our website. The information is only shared between university staff and, at times, between university staff and those responsible for UNB-hosted websites.

In some cases, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of visitors could allow for individual identification. Please check with your Internet Service Provider to learn more about how they use IP addresses.

## myUNB

Our [myUNB](http://my.unb.ca/ "My.UNB") section uses cookies, small pieces of information sent from our site to your web browser. Cookies enable our website to remember personal page view settings. This information is used solely to provide an improved experience for our users. Each browser allows you to set your preferences for accepting or rejecting cookies, as well as for deleting cookies. UNB's Information Technology Services [Help Desk](http://helpdesk.unb.ca/ "Help Desk") can help you find these settings in your browser. 

## Want to know more?

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding privacy or management of personal information at UNB, you can visit the Protection of Personal Information and Privacy @ UNB website, consult the Policy for the Protection of Personal Information and Privacy (.pdf) or contact the [University Secretariat](http://www.unb.ca/secretariat "University Secretariat").
